[{"answer": "Hello.  You have reached the New York Health Center.  Please choos", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": "", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " I hate these machines.  I guess I need to press two", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Hello.  You have reached the New York Health Center.  Please choos", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " NYHC appointment office.  Can I help you", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 29, "question": " I hate these machines.  I guess I need to press two", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Yes, please.  Id like to make an appointment for someone who is sick", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 30, "question": " NYHC appointment office.  Can I help you", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Is this for one of your family members, sir", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Yes, please.  Id like to make an appointment for someone who is sick", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " No, its for a co-worker who doesnt speak much English", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Is this for one of your family members, sir", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " OK, and has he been to our office before", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 36, "question": " No, its for a co-worker who doesnt speak much English", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " No, he doesnt even live here in the U.S", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 37, "question": " OK, and has he been to our office before", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " What is the problem with him", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 38, "question": " No, he doesnt even live here in the U.S", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Hes been having stomach pains for the past 3 days and he feels nauseous", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 39, "question": " What is the problem with him", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " We have an opening tomorrow at 3:00 pm.  Would that work for him", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Hes been having stomach pains for the past 3 days and he feels nauseous", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Ah, no.  I have to drive him to your office and I have a meeting from 2:00 to 4:00", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 41, "question": " We have an opening tomorrow at 3:00 pm.  Would that work for him", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Were totally booked in the morning.  But since it sounds like hes i", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Ah, no.  I have to drive him to your office and I have a meeting from 2:00 to 4:00", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": "0 am and  Dr. Green can try to squeeze him in", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Were totally booked in the morning.  But since it sounds like hes i", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " OK, thats fine", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 48, "question": "0 am and  Dr. Green can try to squeeze him in", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " What is his name", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 49, "question": " OK, thats fine", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Hiro Kanataka", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 50, "question": " What is his name", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Could you spell that please", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Hiro Kanataka", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Sure, its H-I-R-O, first name and K-A-N-A-T-A-K-A, last name", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Could you spell that please", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " And whats his date of birth", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Sure, its H-I-R-O, first name and K-A-N-A-T-A-K-A, last name", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Sorry, I dont know.  I dont know him that well", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 54, "question": " And whats his date of birth", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " All right.  And what kind of health insurance does he have", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Sorry, I dont know.  I dont know him that well", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Actually, I dont know.  He may not have any since hes just visiting or he migh", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 56, "question": " All right.  And what kind of health insurance does he have", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " OK, sir. Please make him aware that if he doesnt have healt", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Actually, I dont know.  He may not have any since hes just visiting or he migh", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Do you know how much it will be without insurance", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 63, "question": " OK, sir. Please make him aware that if he doesnt have healt", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " The fee for the doctors appointment will be $250 and any tests o", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Do you know how much it will be without insurance", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Wow!  I will tell him.  I hope he has insurance", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 70, "question": " The fee for the doctors appointment will be $250 and any tests o", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Can we have a phone number where we can reach him", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Wow!  I will tell him.  I hope he has insurance", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Let me give you mine because he is staying with me right now.  Its 542-6528", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Can we have a phone number where we can reach him", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Is that the 706 area code", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Let me give you mine because he is staying with me right now.  Its 542-6528", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Yes", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Is that the 706 area code", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " And what is your name so we can put it on the file", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Yes", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Its Yoki Shiina", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 76, "question": " And what is your name so we can put it on the file", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Alright Mr. Shiina, we have an appointment for Mr. Kanataka at 9:00 a", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Its Yoki Shiina", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you.  Good-bye", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Alright Mr. Shiina, we have an appointment for Mr. Kanataka at 9:00 a", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Good-bye", "docId": "02-05", "aSentId": 84, "question": " OK.  Thank you.  Good-bye", "qSentId": 83}]
